You already can do a ton with Tableau to explore dataset.
يمكنكم بالفعل القيام بالكثير والكثير مع Tableau لاستكشاف مجموعة البيانات.
The ideas in this lesson will help you with tackling a dataset for
ستساعدكم الأفكار الواردة في هذا الدرس في معالجة مجموعة بيانات
the first time and putting your final products together.
للمرة الأولى ووضع منتجاتكم النهائية معًا.
There are five purposes of this lesson before you move on to
هناك خمسة أغراض لهذا الدرس سنتعلمها، قبل الانتقال إلى
your project and complete your Tableau journey here at Udacity.
مشروعاتكم وإكمال رحلتكم Tableau في Udacity.
We've been working with a single dataset,
لقد عملنا مع مجموعة بيانات واحدة،
but it's important that you feel comfortable with lots of different types of data.
ولكن من المهم الشعور بالراحة مع الكثير من أنواع البيانات المختلفة.
So you will gain practice with that in this lesson.
لذا، ستكتسبون خبرة الممارسة مع تلك البيانات في هذا الدرس.
You will learn about dashboards,
ستتعلمون عن لوحات المعلومات،
which allow you to analyze multiple sheets all at
والتي تسمح لكم بتحليل أوراق متعددة كلها في
the same time and even build filters that act over all of the sheets at once.
نفس الوقت، وأيضًا إنشاء عناصر التصفية التي تعمل على جميع الأوراق في وقت واحد.
You will combine items one and two above to create dashboards for some new datasets.
ستقومون بدمج البندين الأول والثاني المذكورين أعلاه لإنشاء لوحات معلومات لبعض مجموعات البيانات الجديدة.
Don't worry, we'll do this together to build your confidence.
لا تقلق، سنقوم بذلك معًا لبناء ثقتكم بأنفسكم.
That way you get some practice before you tackle the project.
وبهذه الطريقة ستحصلون على بعض التدريب قبل معالجة المشروع.
You will learn about Stories,
ستتعرفون على Stories،
a feature of Tableau that allows you to link together your worksheets and
وهي ميزة في Tableau تسمح لك بربط أوراق العمل
dashboards to give an audience a well-rounded grasp of your insights.
ولوحات المعلومات الخاصة بك لتزويد الجمهور بإدراك جيد لرؤيتكم.
Finally, we will point you some additional resources
وأخيرًا، سنوضح لكم بعض الموارد الإضافية
for you to continue learning and keep your Tableau skills fresh.
لمواصلة التعلم والحفاظ على مهاراتكم في Tableau.
You will be using a few new datasets to complete the questions in this lesson.
ستستخدمون بعض مجموعات البيانات الجديدة لإكمال الأسئلة في هذا الدرس.
So they'll be provided in the Resources tab.
لذا، سيتم توفيرها في علامة التبويب Resources.
A breakdown of the main topics covered in this section are provided below.
وفيما يلي تحليل للموضوعات الرئيسية التي يتناولها هذا القسم.